(Sheldon:)You guys stink.
(Bernadette:)Sorry I flipped out on you.
(Bernadette:)I think it's just hormones.
(Raj:)I think you were mean
before you were pregnant,
(Raj:)but it's fine.
(Raj:)So, uh, instead of
cleaning out the room,
(Raj:)why don't we just decide
on a theme for the nursery?
(Bernadette:)Does it really need one?
(Raj:)Of course it does.
(Raj:)Didn't your baby room
have a theme?
(Bernadette:)Well, it doubled
as my dad's office,
(Bernadette:)and he was a cop,
so I guess the theme was
(Bernadette:)bloody homicide photos.
(Raj:)Oh. Mine was
Winnie the Pooh.
(Raj:)But anyway...
(Raj:)why don't we just
take a step back
and start with a color?
(Raj:)Right? There are
so many amazing ones.
(Raj:)Red, blue, green, purple...
(Bernadette:)Are you just gonna name
all the colors?
(Raj:)Well, not now.
I don't care what color
the room is.
(Raj:)Okay, well, I'm just
trying to help you.
(Bernadette:)Well, you're not,
so just drop it!